mysimon.com 2017-12-31

# CBS Interactive Privacy Policy :: CBS Interactive

##### Last Modified: September 15, 2016

Click to review previous version.

**Note:** The CBS Interactive Privacy Policy has been updated. Please review the updated privacy policy carefully before using the CBS Interactive Web Services. By using any of the CBS Interactive Web Services, you consent to the terms of the updated Privacy Policy. 

Click here for more information about the updates and to review the previous version. 

Welcome to the network of interactive services provided by CBS Interactive Inc., its affiliates and its subsidiaries (collectively “CBS Interactive,” “us,” or “we”). CBS Interactive is committed to protecting your privacy. CBS Interactive owns, operates, or provides access to, several interactive web sites, mobile and connected TV applications , or other online interactive features and services that provide an authorized link or URL to this Privacy Policy (collectively "CBS Interactive Services", or "Services"). This Privacy Policy describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you visit the CBS Interactive Services; how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected. Trust is a cornerstone of our mission at CBS Interactive. We are committed to gaining and maintaining your trust by following a core set of Privacy Principles. 

  1. #### Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information, including contact information, collected about you by the CBS Interactive Services. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review our Terms of Use which governs your use of the CBS Interactive Services.

  2. #### Information Collected

**Information you provide directly to CBS Interactive Services**. You are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit a CBS Interactive Services. CBS Interactive Web Sites may ask you for different types of information when you register for certain services, access various content or features, or directly contact the Services including: 

    * Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, facsimile number, and mobile number;
    * User name, password, and password reminder questions and answers;
    * Age and date of birth;
    * Other demographic information, such as gender, job information, and postal code;
    * Public information, including profile information, you provide to the CBS Interactive Services for publication, such as your user name, comments, likes, interests, status, pictures and the address of your website;
    * Communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive;
    * Search queries;
    * In limited circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number, social security number or comparable national identifiers, and driver's license number where needed for payment, to complete a particular transaction, or to access a particular service (e.g., contests or paid subscriptions);
    * Contact information about others when you provide information about others or refer a friend to a particular website or service (note: such information is used solely to facilitate the communications requested);
    * Information posted in community discussions and other interactive online features;
    * Correspondence you send to us; and
    * Information collected about you offline (including via facsimile, mail, or in person for sweepstakes entrance forms).

**Information we collect automatically on CBS Interactive Services**. CBS Interactive Services may collect certain information automatically, including: 

    * Your device type and settings, software used and browser type and operating system;
    * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
    * Websites or other services you visited before and after visiting a CBS Interactive Services;
    * Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on within CBS Interactive Services;
    * Unique identifiers and connection information, including mobile device identification numbers (e.g. Apple’s Identifier for Advertising IP (IDFA) or Google’s Android Advertising ID (AAID)) and internet connection means (e.g. mobile operator, ISP, WiFi connection) that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law;
    * Information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies;
    * Information about your interactions with audio and video content, such as the type of content listened to (including music applications such as iTunes, Spotify and Last.fm) and content viewed, and information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded;
    * Upon request, your bandwidth speed and information about the software programs installed on your computer including registry key information; and
    * Standard server log information.

**Information we obtain from other sources**. Where permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (e.g., mobile devices, third party services, and embedded audio and video players), from co-branded partners and websites (e.g., on our Facebook pages), and from commercially available sources (e.g., data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources: 

    * Name, postal address, and telephone number;
    * Demographic data, such as age, gender, and income level;
    * If you access third party services (e.g., Facebook, Google+ or Twitter) through a CBS Interactive Service, or if you access a CBS Interactive Service via a third party service, your username and password for those services and other information available about or collected from you on those services, as described in our overview of Video Services and Social Networking Policy
    * Your interests and purchase behavior;
    * Publicly-observed data, such as activities on blogs, videos, and other online postings; and
    * Other navigation data, such as web sites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on.

This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to CBS Interactive. 

**Combining Information**. Please note that all of the information we collect about you may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across the CBS Interactive Services. 

  3. #### Use of Information

We only use payment and identity verification information, such as credit card numbers, driver's license numbers, social security numbers, or comparable national identifiers as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service (e.g., paid subscriptions or awarding prizes to contest winners) or as otherwise required by law.We generally use other information we collect about you to:

    * Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to send you electronic newsletters, authorize a purchase, and complete a transaction that you have requested;
    * Enable you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards;
    * Provide you with electronic newsletters, information, special offers and promotional materials on behalf of CBS Interactive Services, companies within our corporate family, and third parties, in accordance with applicable law;
    * Analyze the use of CBS Interactive Services and information about visitors to our Services to understand and improve our service offerings and, in accordance with our sharing policies, discussed below, to produce or disclose anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop their own products and service offerings;
    * Customize the content you see when you visit a CBS Interactive Services;
    * Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests, as described in our overview of CBS Interactive Online Advertising;
    * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and otherwise in accordance with CBS Interactive's Terms of Use, including restrictions of the use of software to remove, modify, disable, block or otherwise impair any advertising in connection with the Services; and
    * For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.
  4. #### Disclosure of Information

CBS Interactive is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you. 

    * **With your consent.** With your consent, we may share your contact information with third party marketing partners. For example, CBS Interactive Services such as ZDNet.com and TechRepublic.com offer free access to relevant services (e.g., webcasts and white papers) if you allow your information to be shared with third parties so that they can contact you by email, telephone, postal mail or other common communication methods about their products or services.
    * **Authorized third party service providers.** We share your contact information with third party vendors who help us with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, suppression list management and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your contact information to help us provide our services and not for any other purpose. Also, authorized third party service providers may collect non-contact information about your visits to our Services with cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies that may be used to deliver advertisements or marketing tailored to your interests or, in connection with other data about you including data regarding your use of websites, apps or other services over time and across the Internet, to determine the connections that may exist among different devices. For example, if your IP address is associated with multiple devices (such as smartphones, connected TVs, tablets and so on), these services providers may determine that you, as a user, are connected to such devices. For more information, visit our overview on cookies, web beacons and other technologies (including Do Not Track).
    * **Sweepstakes, contests, or promotions.** When you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, and in accordance with the terms and conditions of the promotions, your information may be disclosed to our sponsors and third parties who help design, administer and implement the promotion, including in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment and aggregated data analysis. Your information also may be disclosed as required by law, such as on a winners list. Further, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, including allowing our sponsors to use your name, voice, and likeness in advertising and marketing associated with the promotion in accordance with applicable law. All terms applicable to the particular promotion will be made available to you at the time you enter the promotion.
    * **Co-Branded Partners.** Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom a CBS Interactive Service may jointly offer a service or feature. You can tell when you are accessing a service or feature offered by a Co-Branded Partner because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. In doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may also apply to its use of your information.
    * **CBS Interactive Services and other CBS businesses.** CBS Interactive and other business units of CBS Corporation, our parent company, continue to expand their online presence in order to offer users rich and deep interactive experiences. Where permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you within the family of CBS Interactive Services and with [CBS Corporation](http://www.cbscorporation.com/), our parent company, and other [CBS-affiliated companies](http://www.cbscorporation.com/portfolio), so that we can provide you with information about products and services that might interest you. 
    * **Business transfers.** We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a CBS Interactive Service, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
    * **Legal requirements.** We may disclose information about our users, including contact information, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures, and to comply with other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements.
    * **Protect our Services and users.** We may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of CBS Interactive Services, other CBS companies, and their employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements); to protect the safety and security of users of the Services and members of the public; and as otherwise disclosed in our Terms of Use.

Please note that we may share information with advertisers as described in our overview of CBS Interactive Online Advertising. In addition, information collected about your interactions with audio and video content may be shared with third parties, including social networking services, such as Facebook, and video measurement and subscription services, including Nielsen TV Rating, as described in our Video Services and Social Networking Policy. Finally, we also may share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties, to help us develop content and services we hope will interest you or to help these third parties develop their own products and service offerings including targeted marketing as described in our overview of Third Party Online Advertising.

  5. #### Your Choices

You can choose to enjoy content and features on CBS Interactive Services without providing us directly with any information about you; however, as described above, some information may be collected automatically or be requested so that you can take advantage of certain features and services offered on CBS Interactive Services.You can opt out of receiving commercial email or text messages from a particular CBS Interactive Services or other service by following the instructions contained in any such message or by contacting us directly. Please note that even if you unsubscribe to commercial messages, we may still need to send you communications relating to your use of the CBS Interactive Web Sites, such as service announcements.You also have choices about whether cookies and other similar technologies are placed on your computer or mobile device. For more information, visit our overview on cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies (including Do Not Track).You also may choose to opt out of use of data that our authorized third party service providers or we collect about your visits to our business partners’ websites that may be used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests. To opt out, visit the CBS Interactive Business Partner Advertising Opt-Out page.Finally, you also have choices about the collection and use of your information by third parties to display relevant advertisements, as described in our overview of Third Party Online Advertising. 

  6. #### Access

If you choose to share contact information with us, you may have the opportunity to update that information on a CBS Interactive Service. You also may update or amend your information by contacting us. If you ask us to shut down your account or delete your information, we will disable your account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that we may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy our legal and security obligations. For example, some of your information may remain in back-up storage even if you ask us to delete it. In some cases, you may be entitled under local laws to access or object to the processing of information that we hold relating to you. 

  7. #### Protection of Information

We are committed to protecting your information. We have adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident using CBS Interactive Services but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Please refer to the [U.S. Federal Trade Commission's web site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data/idt.shtm) for information on how to protect yourself from identity theft. 

  8. #### Transfer of Data Internationally

CBS Interactive is headquartered in the United States and has affiliate offices and partners in other countries. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the CBS Interactive Services may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in the country to which your information is transferred may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using and participating in any CBS Interactive Services or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, internationaltransfer, storage, and processing of your information. 

  9. #### Visitors from Outside the United States

For additional information about CBS Interactive's privacy practices, as well as our affiliate offices and partners in some of the other countries where we operate, please click on the appropriate link for your jurisdiction: Australia, Canada, the United Kingdom. 

  10. #### California Visitors

For additional information for residents of the State of California click here. 

  11. #### Privacy Protections for Children

Most CBS Interactive Services are intended for a general audience and do not knowingly collect or store contact information about children under the age of 13. Some CBS Interactive Services may ask for your full date of birth date to ensure that they are not collecting information from children under 13 or to identify when additional steps may need to be taken when information has been collected from children under 18. In those instances where a CBS Interactive Service has actual knowledge that it collects information from children or offers a service directed toward children as defined under applicable laws, it will comply with those laws. To read about our privacy policy for children, please see the Children's Privacy Policy. 

  12. #### User-Generated Content

Some CBS Interactive Services enable users to submit their own content for use in contests, blogs, on-air radio and TV broadcasts, online audio and video streams, videos, message boards, and other functions. Publication of User Generated Content on the CBS Interactive Services is subject to our Terms of Use. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and exercise caution when choosing to disclose your contact, financial, and other information in a submission. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety. You should also be aware that we may also engage a third party to provide some of the services associated with the blogs, message boards and similar functions. This third party will collect and host the information that you submit to the CBS Interactive Services but will not use any of this information for purposes other than providing the service. 

  13. #### Third Party Websites and Services

Please note that some CBS Interactive Services may contain links to other websites and services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each website that you visit. When you select a link to a third party web site from one of the CBS Interactive Services (e.g., if you link to PayPal to pay for a product or service offered by a CBS Interactive Service), you will be leaving the CBS Interactive Service. Any information that you disclose on the third party website will be governed by that website's privacy policy. 

  14. #### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will update the "Last Modified Date" and such changes will be effective upon posting. If we make any material changes in the way we use your information, we will notify you by email through the email address you most recently provided to us or by prominently posting a prominent notice of the changes on the CBS Interactive Services. 

  15. #### Questions

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us and we will endeavor to respond to your request within a reasonable period of time. You may also submit questions or comments using the postal address listed below: 

CBS Interactive Inc. 235 Second Street San Francisco, CA 94105 USA Legal Department

For international users, please select this link to find the address of your closest CBS Interactive office. We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any privacy concern. 

[ x ] Close
